<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="saaz">
        <item>Any musical instrument can be credited with popularizing many artists because of how well they play it.
Then, there are some artists that can be credited with popularizing a musical instrument itself because they pioneered its music.
Presenting the legendary Grammy winner Pt. Vikku Vinayak Ram as the headliner for Saaz, the classical night for Alcheringa 2017: Eternal Sands.</item>
        <item>Institute Auditorium</item>\
        <item>2nd February. 7:15 pm to 8:45 pm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="blitz">
        <item>Coke Studio presents Blitzkrieg headlined by Javed Ali at Alcheringa, IIT Guwahati. The time has come to dance your way along the mellifluous tunes of this legend.</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>4th February 8.15 pm to 10.00 pm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="crescendo">
        <item>Crescendo headlined by Sajid Wajid in their first ever college show at Alcheringa, IIT Guwahati. Get ready to get blown away this Alcher dancing to some of the most popular songs from the biggest hits in bollywood!</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>5th February 7:30 pm to 10.30 pm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="juggernaut">
        <item>  Carl Nunes, Latin America’s biggest electronic music artist coming all the way from Guatemala. In his first show on his India tour, catch Carl Nunes live on the main stage as one of our headlining artists on Friday.
Artist managed by Kreative Keeda and NCM.</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>3rd February. 7:15 pm to 8:45 pm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="juggernaut2">
        <item>Presenting Italian phenomena, MARNIK, who have made their mark as one of the most promising talents in today’s scene. Catch Marnik live on the main stage as one of our headlining artists on Friday</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
            <item>3rd February 8.45 pm to 9:15 pm</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mad">
        <item> Easily recognizable through its piano-centred, synthesizer-heavy sound, The MadHatter Project writes, plays and (re)interprets music in its cynically optimistic way. With four history and music geeks (and oxymoron enthusiasts) in its ranks, the product is quirky and flamboyant yet introverted and introspective </item>
        <item>SAC Wall</item>
        <item>4th February  15:30-16:30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="echo">
        <item> A duo of music producers, creating together a mad mix of ethnic backgrounds with electronic bass music, dub and hip hop. ECHO is a singer/MC, and TITO is a real sonic explorer/musician </item>
        <item>Institute Auditorium</item>
        <item>3rd February. 17:30-18:30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="nuno">
        <item>Nuno Marino, guitarist,music composer,padagogue,investor,promoter hailing from Portugal. </item>
        <item>SAC Wall</item>
        <item>3rd February. 16.00 to 17.00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hip">
        <item>Renowned Belly Dance Troup from Delhi, The Hip Circle.</item>
        <item>Institute Auditorium</item>
        <item>15.30 to 16.30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="raymond">
        <item> A lecture by Mr. Raymond O.Cadwell, resident director and full-time professor at Howard University.
Raymond has toured internationally as a performer and director of several shows on gender based equality and advancing the role of women in contemporary society.</item>
        <item>Conference Hall</item>
        <item>4th February. 9:00 to 10:00 am</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="color_ne">
        <item>The time has come to not only enjoy the cultures of the Eternal Sands but also to take pride in our very own culture. And in what better way than to witness live Bihu and Sattriya dance performances.</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>4th February. 16:30 to 18:30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="fails">
        <item>A high energy live show, critical acclaim complete with am aggressive dark brand of metal. All you metal heads out there, rejoice! Coming all away from Canada on Day2.</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>4th Feb</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="soul">
        <item>Soul twins, finalists of Maruti Suzuki, Colours of Youth S04 are back in action known for their fusion style dancing, Bishnu Chetri and Sumit Kumar Jogi are all said to rock the stage with thei hip hop performance</item>
        <item>Cricket Ground</item>
        <item>5th Feb</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="blind_date">
        <item>Participate in this couple event and feel the spark.</item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hungergames">
        <item>Do you have an appetite? Do you have a thing for taste, or do you have a habit of winning? Any of these and you are fit to enter the games.</item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="crush">
        <item>Think you are the best couple around? Compete against other couples and find out!</item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mysterypong">
        <item>Try to get your opponents to drink our famous  Mystery Juice. Trust me, you dont want to drink it, but you will surely want others to!</item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="balloonomia">
        <item>Nobody can be boring with a balloon. So, enjoy yourself through these games. </item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gamingarena">
        <item>In this event we have something for our sports lovers, mixture of desi and videsi.</item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="speeddating">
        <item>Looking for your someone special but don’t have time for that? Take part in our speed dating and find the person missing from your  </item>
        <item>________</item>
        <item>________</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>